Istora Mandiri: Hello, and welcome to Ethereum Classic Community Call number 53. Today is Friday, May 29th, 2026.
Istora Mandiri: ETC Community Calls is a open voice chat discussion about Ethereum Classic, and everyone's welcome.
Istora Mandiri: The call will be published on YouTube, so we kindly ask that discussion stays focused on ideas rather than individuals. Let's keep it classy.
Istora Mandiri: You can find past episodes, transcripts, subscribe to the calendar, and more at cc.theoremclassic.org.
Istora Mandiri: Before the call today, for about an hour, we were in the green room playing with Veritas' poker
Istora Mandiri: DAP, which, we successfully deposited chips, played some rounds of poker, and withdrew from the app in a decentralized format using ETC network. So that was a quite cool experience.
Istora Mandiri: veritas, would you like to…
Istora Mandiri: Have a word about what we just did, and what your project's about?
IAV: I think you'll better describe it.
Istora Mandiri: Okay, well, Veritas has been in the Discord and sharing this, this poker app.
Istora Mandiri: And it's a kind of combination of a chat room.
Istora Mandiri: Where you use your wallet to sign in to the app, and it uses…
Istora Mandiri: your Web3 address as identity validation, and then from there, you can Talk.